XP: Well, we got a lot done!
XP: I think we're ready.
Chicago: Yep!
Chicago: I didn't know IE 6 ran a store.
2000: Me neither!
Chicago: I bet it’s one of the craziest.
Chicago: It’s all so enthusiastic.
2000: I can tell...
ME: I still can’t believe it’s been 25 years.
ME: It feels like yesterday.
2000: Same for me.
95: Now that makes me feel old.
ME: Haha.
Vista: Oh yeah, how's the trip plan?
95: Ah, I got it organized.
95: We're going hiking!
Vista: Good to hear!
2000: Things are flowing well!
Chicago: Agreed.
Chicago: Tomorrow's a surprise.
Chicago: Also, where are we putting our gifts?
95: We're putting them in the party area.
95: We'll prepare there as well.
Chicago: Ah, alright.
XP: The sun's setting soon.
XP: Should we go now?
95: I think so.
95: Let's go.
Chicago: Alright, let's prepare.
98: Ah, another morning!
98: The sun's bright today.
98: Let me go get some breakfast.
98: Hmm, what should I eat?
98: Let me try something a bit unique.
98: Aha!
98: Oh, what?
98: Just a second!
98: Oh, hey!
Chicago: Bonjour!
Chicago: Just wanted to let you know.
Chicago: The hike is now confirmed.
98: Oh, great!
98: When are we leaving?
Chicago: We're thinking around 1 PM.
Chicago: What do you think?
98: Sounds good.
98: I'm having breakfast at the moment.
Chicago: Ah, got it.
98: Say thanks to 95 for me.
Chicago: Alright.
Chicago: See you then!
98: See you!
98: That was fast.
98: Let me get a plate.
98: Wow, that was delicious.
95: Alright, almost done!
95: I still need to find a tent.
95: Let me see if I have one.
95: Hmm...
95: Not here either.
95: I guess I don't have it.
95: I always store my stuff here.
95: Let me call 3.1.
3.1: Hello?
95: Hey, 3.1.
95: Just wanted to ask if you have a tent.
95: I don’t think I have one.
3.1: I don't have one, unfortunately.
3.1: But I think Redstone has some.
95: Ah, alright.
95: Thanks!
3.1: No problem.
95: All done!
95: Just right on time.
95: Let me check
if anyone's here.
95: Woah.
95: You guys are fast.
7: Haha.
Chicago: All of us are here now.
95: Alright.
XP: Who's gonna be driving, by the way?
95: I think we need at least three.
95: I have mine, so I figure two left.
98: I'll go start my car.
XP: I'll go as well.
95: Alright, thanks!
95: Alright, let's go!